Guide to the International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Fishermen and Allied Workers Division, Local 3 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- INTERNATIONAL FISHERMEN AND ALLIED WORKERS OF AMERICA. PACIFIC DISTRICT. LOCAL #3, 1936-1958; RECORDS SUBGROUP 4 (Box-folder 6/9-12/23)
  - MINUTES, 1939-1950; SERIES III (Box-folder 6/20-7/2, 7/7-7/9, 7/11-7/22, 7/25-7/33, 7/35, 7/37)
    - Unit #8 - Gig Harbor, 1948 (Box-folder 7/32)
    - Unit #1 - Tacoma, 1948 (Box-folder 7/33)
    - Unit #4 - Seattle, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 7/35)
    - Crab Unit Minutes, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7/37)
  - SUBJECT SERIES - NORTHWEST SHOREWORKERS COUNCIL, 1946-1950; SERIES IV (Box-folder 7/3-7/6)
    - Subject Files - Northwest Shoreworkers Council (1 of 4), 1946-1950 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Subject Files - Northwest Shoreworkers Council (2 of 4), 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Subject Files - Northwest Shoreworkers Council (3 of 4), 1946-1950 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Subject Files - Northwest Shoreworkers Council (4 of 4), circa 1947 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - ASSORTED INTEROFFICE FILES, 1946-1950; SERIES V (Box-folder 7/10, 7/36)
    - Assorted Interoffice Files, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Assorted Trials. Executive Board. Unit Meetings. Conventions, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7/36)
  - CONTRACT NEGOTIATIONS, 1949; SERIES VI (Box-folder 8/1-8/3)
    - Herring Negotiations, 1949 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Deep Sea Trawl Negotiations, 1949 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Tendermen's Negotiations, 1949 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - WORKING AGREEMENTS, 1939-1950; SERIES VII (Box-folder 8/4-9/8, 9/10-9/21, 9/23-9/28, 10/2-10/3, 10/5, 10/7-10/11)
    - Sardine Agreement, 1946 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Deep Sea Trawl Agreement, 1946 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Sardine Working Agreement, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Salmon Purse Seiners Working Agreement, 1944, 1946 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - Tuna Working Agreement, 1946 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - Sardine Working Agreement, 1945 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - Southeast Alaska Salmon Agreement, 1945 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Albacore Agreement, 1945 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Local 33 Working Agreement, 1943 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Assorted-Union Membership, Charter Party Agreement, Reduction and Saltery Workers Local 7, circa 1943-circa 1945 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Southwest Alaska Prices and Salmon Purse Seine Agreement, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - 1950 Alaska Salmon Agreement (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Assorted - Local #54 Gray's Harbor, Cannery Workers, International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Columbia River Fishermen's Protective Union, Columbia Rivers Fishermen's Protective Union, Fish Reduction Workers, agreements with the Dungeness Crab Company., 1943, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - Deep Sea Trawlers, circa 1950 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Alaska King Crab and Related Species. Trawlers, 1946-1950 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Purse Seiners Working Agreement, 1950 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - Agreement with Fish Reduction and Saltery Workers, 1939 (Box-folder 8/20)
    - Assorted - United Fish and Cannery Worker's Union Local #7, Fish Reduction and Saltery Workers Local #7, various Unions' Agreements with Alaska Salmon Industry Inc., Spanish Wage Agreement., 1950 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - Crab Agreement, 1949 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - Herring Agreement, 1949 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Salmon Purse Seine Boats, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 8/24)
    - Salmon Purse Seine Boats (1 of 2), 1949 (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Salmon Purse Seine Boats (2 of 2 ), 1949 (Box-folder 8/26)
    - Tendermen's Agreement, 1949 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - Salmon Purse Seine Boats (1 of 3), 1948 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - Salmon Purse Seine Boats (2 of 3), 1948 (Box-folder 8/29)
    - Salmon Purse Seine Boats (3 of 3), 1948 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - with Alaska Salmon Industry Inc., 1942 (Box-folder 8/31)
    - Negotiations with Affiliated Unions, Canned Salmon Industry, and National War Labor Board, 1942 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Deep Sea Trawl Working Agreement, 1947 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Crab Agreement, 1948 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Local 33 Sardine, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Otter Trawlers, 1943 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Working Agreement Info. (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Salmon Purse Seine Boats (1 of 3), 1947 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Salmon Purse Seine Boats (2 of 3), 1947 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Salmon Purse Seine Boats (3 of 3), 1947 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (1 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (2 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (3 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (4 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (5 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (6 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (7 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (8 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (9 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (10 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Puget Sound Salmon (11 of 11), 1950 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Tendermen's Agreement, 1948 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - Reduction and Saltery Workers #7, 1948 (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Herring Agreement, 1947 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Crab Agreements, 1945-1948 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Tendermen's Agreement, 1947 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - Assorted-Shoreworker's Council, Fish Reduction and Saltery Workers Local #3, Otter Trawlers, Alaska Fishermen's Union, Albacore Fishing Agreement, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 9/28)
    - Herring Agreement, 1949 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Sardine Agreement, 1948 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Assorted- Alaska Salmon Industry Inc. and Various Cannery, Packing, Salting, and Reduction Unions., 1947-1949 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - Agreement for Southeastern Alaska, 1940 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Alaska Fishermen's Union Bristol Bay Agreement, 1961 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Alaska Fishermen's Union General Agreement, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Reefer Agreement, 1961 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Assorted 1956-1957 Agreements (Box-folder 10/11)
  - PRICE AGREEMENTS, 1941-1950; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 9/9, 10/1, 10/4, 10/19-10/41)
    - Southwestern Alaska Seine Fish, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Sardine Agreement, 1948 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Deep Sea Trawl Prices, 1947 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Fresh Fish Agreement, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Kodiak Agreement, 1941 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Fresh Fish Agreement, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 10/21)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Agreement, 1948 (Box-folder 10/22)
    - Fresh fish Agreement, 1948 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - Sardine Agreement, 1947 (Box-folder 10/24)
    - Southeastern Alaska Price Agreement, 1948 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Southwest Alaska Salmon Agreement, 1947 (Box-folder 10/26)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Agreement, 1947 (Box-folder 10/27)
    - Fresh Fish Agreement, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 10/28)
    - Sardine Price Agreement, 1946 (Box-folder 10/29)
    - Southwest Alaska Salmon Agreement, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10/30)
    - 1946 Deep Sea Trawl Price Agreement and associated correspondence, 1943, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10/31)
    - Fresh Fish Agreement, 1946 (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Agreement, 1946 (Box-folder 10/33)
    - Fresh Fish Agreement, 1945 (Box-folder 10/34)
    - Herring Agreement, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 10/35)
    - Assorted. includes petitions and statements supporting an increate to 1949-season herring quota., 1948-1949 (Box-folder 10/36)
    - Salmon Agreement (1 of 2), 1949 (Box-folder 10/37)
    - Salmon Agreement (2 of 2), 1949 (Box-folder 10/38)
    - Deep Sea Trawl, 1949 (Box-folder 10/39)
    - Sardine Agreement, 1949 (Box-folder 10/40)
    - Shark Agreement, 1949 (Box-folder 10/41)
  - PRICE NEGOTIATIONS, 1948-1950; SERIES IX (Box-folder 9/22, 10/6, 10/12-10/18)
    - Season Price Negotiations Ballots for Salmon, 1948 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Southwest Alaska Prices, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Southwest Alaska Prices, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Herring Negotiations, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Deep Sea Trawlers, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Purse Seine Negotiations and Strike, 1949 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - Sardine Price Negotiation, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Herring Negotiations, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 10/17)
    - Puget Sound Price Negotiations, 1949 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1937-1950; SERIES X (Box-folder 7/23, 11/1-11/2, 11/4-11/14)
    - Per Capita Receipts, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7/23)
    - Financial Statements, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Financial Reports, 1945, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - U.S. Withholding Tax, 1946 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Catch, 1943, 1947 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1947-1947 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Taxes, 1947 (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Taxes, 1948 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Financial Information, 1948 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Taxes, 1949 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Ledger - Receipts and Disbursements, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Ledger, 1950 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Taxes (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Financial Reports, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - SHIPWRECK BENEFITS, 1938-1942, 1944; SERIES XI (Box-folder 11/3, 11/15)
    - War Risk Insurance, 1944 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Shipwreck Benefits, 1938-1942 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - IFAWA TRIALS AND CLAIMS, 1942-1948; SERIES XII (Box-folder 19/5-19/8)
    - Claims Settled, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Claims Pending, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Claims Pending, 1946 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Assignments and Claims, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - NEWSLETTERS - "IFAWA Views the News" and Bulletins, 1941-1942; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 11/16)
  - STRIKE FILES - IFAWA Local #3 Strike, October 1949, SERIES XIV (Box-folder 11/17)
  - CONFERENCES AND CONVENTIONS, 1944-1950; SERIES XV (Box-folder 11/18-11/29, 12/1-12/2)
    - Sixth Annual Convention, December 1944 (Box-folder 11/18)
    - Juneau Conference with IFAWA and FTA Representatives, March 18 1949 (Box-folder 11/19)
    - Assorted - Second Annual Fishermen's Fiesta, Eighth Annual Convention, Alaska CIO Conference, Third Annual Local #3, 1944, 1946, 1948 (Box-folder 11/20)
    - Local #3 Conference, 1948 (Box-folder 11/21)
    - Local #3 Conference (1949) and related organizational, financial, and working agreement items., 1944, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 11/22)
    - Ninth Annual Convention, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 11/23)
    - Conferences and Conventions, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 11/24)
    - Eighth and Ninth Annual Conventions, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 11/25)
    - Seventh Annual Convention, 1946 (Box-folder 11/26)
    - Eleventh Annual Convention, 1950 (Box-folder 11/27)
    - Alaska Purse Seiners Annual Convention, 1937 (Box-folder 11/28)
    - 33rd Annual, International Seamen's Union of America, 1936 (Box-folder 11/29)
    - Fifth Annual Convention, 1943 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Convention Booklets, 1940-1943 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - EXECUTIVE BOARD MINUTES, 1941-1950; SERIES XVI (Box-folder 12/3-12/14)
    - Executive Board Minutes, January 18 1948 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1947 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1944 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1949 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1945 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1947 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1949 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1946 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1948 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 12/14)
- NORTHWEST IFAWA COUNCIL, 1936, 1948-1950; RECORDS SUBGROUP 5 (Box-folder 12/15-12/19)
  - Constitution. Minutes, 1948 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Minutes, 1949 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Minutes, 1948 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Clippings from Newspapers Re: Purse Seining, Fish Bills, etc., 1936-1937 (Box-folder 12/19)
- FEDERATED FISHERMEN'S COUNCIL OF THE PACIFIC COAST, 1937-1944; RECORDS SUBGROUP 6 (Box-folder 12/21-12/23)
  - First Annual Convention, 1937 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - 2nd Annual Federated Fishermen's Council of the Pacific Coast Convention, Executive Board Minutes, CIO National Maritime Unity Conference Minutes, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - National War Labor Board - in the Matter of Alaska Salmon Industry Inc., and Alaska Fishermen's Union and Other Unions, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 12/23)
- INTERNATIONAL LONGSHOREMEN'S AND WAREHOUSEMEN'S UNION. INTERNATIONAL. FISHERMEN AND ALLIED WORKERS DIVISION. LOCAL #3., 1938-1982; RECORDS SUBGROUP 7 (Box-folder 13/1-17/17)
  - ORGANIZATIONAL FEATURES, 1956-1974; SERIES I (Box-folder 13/1-13/8)
    - By Laws and Constitution, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Constitution, 1956, 1965 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - By Laws, circa 1959 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - By-Laws and Constitution, circa 1961-1973 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Revised Constitution and Seniority Rules, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Revised Local #3 Constitution, 1957 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Local #3 Constitution-Draft (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Local #3 Revised Constitution, 1974 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - MEMBERSHIP LISTS, 1950-1951; SERIES II (Box-folder 13/9)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, circa 1953-1982; SERIES III (Box-folder 13/10-13/21, 13/30)
    - Herring Workers Correspondence, 1954, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Forms and Notices, circa 1962-circa 1967 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - National Labor Relations Board-Correspondence and Complaint, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - National Labor Relations Board - Bornstein Seafoods, Inc. and ILWU Local #3 Case, 1955 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - National Labor Relations Board- Packing and Canneries, 1973, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - National Labor Relations Board- American Freezership, Inc. MV Theresa Lee Vote, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/15)
    - National Labor Relations Board- Perfection Smokery Recognition as Union, 1976 (Box-folder 13/16)
    - National Labor Relations Board- Pan Alaskan Fisheries, 1966-1967, 1974 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Assorted, 1962, 1964, 1975, 1978 (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Alaska Herring Products- Correspondence and Payments Re: Financial Statement, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Assorted Correspondence, Agreements and Political Issues, circa 1953-1956, 1963-1967, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Convention, Executive Board Minutes, News, Correspondence to Membership, 1966 Otter Trawl Agreement, 1966, 1977, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Strike Mileage Correspondence, 1950 (Box-folder 13/30)
  - MINUTES, 1950-1952; SERIES IV (Box-folder 13/22-13/29, 13/31-13/43)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Local Bellingham, 1950 (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Local Seattle, 1950 (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Local Anacortes, 1950 (Box-folder 13/24)
    - ILWU Local #3-3 Conference, 1950 (Box-folder 13/25)
    - Security Regulations Protest Meeting Minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 13/26)
    - Local #3-3 Special Meeting Minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 13/27)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers of America-Local Everett, 1950 (Box-folder 13/28)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Local Gig Harbor, 1950 (Box-folder 13/29)
    - Special Herring Meeting Minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 13/31)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Local Tacoma, 1950 (Box-folder 13/32)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Annual Conference, 1951 (Box-folder 13/33)
    - Joint Negotiations Committee, Deep Sea Crew, Special Meeting Minutes, 1951 (Box-folder 13/34)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Local Bellingham, 1951 (Box-folder 13/35)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Local Seattle, 1951 (Box-folder 13/36)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division - Local Anacortes, 1951 (Box-folder 13/37)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division - Local Everett, 1951 (Box-folder 13/38)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division - Local Gig Harbor, 1951 (Box-folder 13/39)
    - Special Herring Division Meeting Minutes, 1951 (Box-folder 13/40)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Tendermen, 1951 (Box-folder 13/41)
    - Fishermen and Allied Workers Division-Local Tacoma, 1951 (Box-folder 13/42)
    - Executive Board. Contract Committee, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 13/43)
  - CONTRACT NEGOTIATIONS, 1945-1980; SERIES V (Box-folder 14/1-14/33)
    - Local 3 Pacific American Fisheries, Inc. Injunction and Skrivanich/Shulich and Gazija/Gazija Case, 1945-1952 (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Memo on San Francisco Sardine Operations, 1950 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Canners Association Negotiations, 1957 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Tendermen Negotiations, 1957 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Wakefield Deep Sea Contract Negotiations, 1957 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Seiners Negotiations, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Tendermen's Negotiations, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Puget Sound Plant/Cannery Workers Negotiations, 1956 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Salmon Working Agreement Negotiations and Arbitration, 1956 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Herring Negotiations, 1956 (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Puget Sound Salmon- Cannery and Tendermen's Contract Negotiations, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Southwestern Alaska Seine Fish Price, 1951 (Box-folder 14/12)
    - International Pacific Halibut Commission- Press Releases, Regulations, Annual Report 1977, Scientific Reports: Factors Affecting Longline Catch and Effort, Abundance and Fishing Mortality of Pacific Halibut, Relation of Fecundity to Long-Term Changes in Growth, Abundance and Recruitment, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Southwestern Alaska Seine Fishermen, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Herring Negotiations, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Negotiations and Court Documents, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Winter Herring Agreement- Equal Wages for Alaskan Residents/Non-Residents, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Herring Shoreworkers Negotiations and Contract Cancellations, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Southwest Alaska Salmon Negotiations, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 14/19)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Negotiations and Court Documents, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Workers Negotiations, 1953 (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Working Agreement Negotiations and Correspondence, 1953 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Tendermen and Cannery Workers' Negotiations, 1953 (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Fish Reduction and Saltery Workers Union Negotiations, 1953 (Box-folder 14/24)
    - Seine and Gillnet Agreement Legal Advice, 1954 (Box-folder 14/25)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Workers and Tendermen's Negotiations, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 14/26)
    - Southwest Alaska Salmon Negotiations, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 14/27)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Workers and Tendermen Negotiations, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 14/28)
    - Tendermen's Negotiations, 1955 (Box-folder 14/29)
    - Herring Negotiations, 1959 (Box-folder 14/30)
    - Working Agreement Negotiations and Correspondence, 1955 (Box-folder 14/31)
    - Deep Sea Negotiations, 1956 (Box-folder 14/32)
    - Herring Plant Workers Negotiations, 1956 (Box-folder 14/33)
  - WORKING AGREEMENTS, 1938-1980; SERIES VI (Box-folder 14/34-14/54, 15/1-15/45)
    - Herring Fishermen and Plant Workers, 1957-1958, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 14/34)
    - Puget Sound Crab Processors Agreement, 1954, 1962 (Box-folder 14/35)
    - Blaine Fish Reduction Agreement and Dahl Fish Co./Borenstein Seafoods and Seafood Workers of Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 14/36)
    - Herring, Alaska King Crab Processing, ILWU Local #37, Fish Canneries Agreements, 1957, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 14/37)
    - Agreements: United Packinghouse Workers, Fish Reduction and Saltery Workers, Dragboat and Otter Trawler, Reef Net Tendermen, Alaska Salmon Industry, Sacramento River, South Eastern Alaska Purse Seiners, Bellingham Cannery Workers, Sardine Workers, Puget Sound Crab Processors, 1951, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 14/38)
    - Alaska King Crab/Deep Sea Trawler Agreements, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 14/39)
    - Sardine Price Negotiations, 1950 (Box-folder 14/40)
    - Sardine Price Agreement, 1950 (Box-folder 14/41)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Worker Agreement, 1950 (Box-folder 14/42)
    - Kodiak Resident Cannery Workers Agreement, Puget Sound Salmon Canners Tendermen's Agreement, Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association Agreement, 1961-1962, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 14/43)
    - University of Washington Research Agreement, n.d. (Box-folder 14/44)
    - Office and Professional Employees Local No. 8, 1965 (Box-folder 14/45)
    - Fish Reduction. Herring Plant Workers. Herring Fishermen., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 14/46)
    - Reefnetters, 1938 (Box-folder 14/47)
    - Otter Trawl Agreement, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 14/48)
    - Plant Workers, 1962 (Box-folder 14/49)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Workers, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 14/50)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Workers, 1971 (Box-folder 14/51)
    - Southwest Alaska Agreements, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 14/52)
    - Puget Sound Salmon, 1951 (Box-folder 14/53)
    - Crab Agreements, 1951 (Box-folder 14/54)
    - Tendermen's Agreement, 1951 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Herring Agreements, 1951 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Sardine Fishing Operations in the San Francisco Area, 1950 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - International Longshoremen and Warehousemen Local 37 with related material including, 1979 Meeting of the International Pacific Salmon Fisheries Commissions, Predictions of 1979 Pink Salmon Runs to the Fraser River, Predictions of 1979 Sockeye and Pink Salmon Runs to the Fraser River, 1971, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Request for Affidavits. Herring Agreements. Pay Records., 1961 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Pan Alaska Fisheries Inc. Alaska Packers Association. Puget Sound Fish Cannery Workers, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Herring Fishermen, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Dock Watchmen, 1973 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Tendermen's Agreements, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Salmon Agreement, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Salmon Working Agreements, 1958 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - ILWU Local #142 (Honolulu, HI) Dental, Medical Plans, Agreements, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - AFL Cannery Workers, ILWU Cannery Workers, ILWU Tendermen, Herring Supplemental and Plant Workers Agreements, 1956 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Tendermen Agreement, Fishermen's Packing Corporation Cannery Workers Agreement, Correspondence Re: Health and Welfare Benefits and Vacation Pay, 1956 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Puget Sound Fish Cannery Workers Agreement, Legal Advise, Correspondence re: Health and Welfare Benefits and Vacation Pay, 1956 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Herring Shoreworkers Fish Reduction and Saltery Workers Agreement, 1955 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - Reefer King Fisheries, Inc. Health and Welfare Schedule, 1965 (Box-folder 15/17)
    - Herring Plant Workers Agreements- Edible Herring Products, Storfold and Grondahl Pkg. Co., Crab Bay Packers, Oceania Fisheries, Buchan Packing Co., 1956 (Box-folder 15/18)
    - Herring Agreements- Edible Herring Products, Oceania Fisheries, Crab Bay Packers, Buchan Packing, Fishing Pool Agreement, 1956 (Box-folder 15/19)
    - Puget Sound Cannery Workers Agreements, Legal Correspondence, Membership List, 1946-1952 (Box-folder 15/20)
    - Herring Agreement, Fish Reduction and Saltery Workers Agreement, Correspondence, 1952 (Box-folder 15/21)
    - False Pass and Port Moller Signed Working Agreements, Puget Sound Salmon Workers Agreement, 1952 (Box-folder 15/22)
    - Southwest Alaska Salmon Agreements, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 15/23)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Agreement and Signed Owners Agreements, 1952 (Box-folder 15/24)
    - Puget Sound Salmon Negotiations and Proposed Agreement, 1952 (Box-folder 15/25)